Welcome back to my series where I
recreate Dairy Queen Blizzard flavors,
but lower in calories and higher in
protein. This is the Confetti Cake
Blizzard. Let me show you how to make
it. I think that I've truly nailed the
soft serve recipe that Dairy Queen uses.
It comes out perfect every single time.
The texture is on point. It does not get
better. So, I will have that full recipe
down in the caption below as always.
Now, for the confetti cake pieces, I'm
using these birthday cake cookie dough
bites. Obviously, I know they're not the
cake pieces like Dairy Queen uses, but I
don't think you're going to find protein
cake bites anywhere. So, this is what
we're going with. I just found them on
Tik Tok shop, honestly. I use about half
a package, which is about 135 calories,
8 g of protein, which makes them the
perfect addition to this flavor. And
also, feel free to add some sprinkles or
confetti pieces, whatever you want.
Comment what flavors you want me to
recreate